<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Progetti di architettura e ingegneria]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Progetti di architettura e ingegneria]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/archingstudio/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 08:48:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/archingstudio/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MRADI designS KENYA INTO AN ITALIAN/SWAHILI STYLE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>MRADI designS KENYA INTO AN ITALIAN/SWAHILI STYLE</h1><p>Our aim is to merge principles of architecture and renewable energy with local culture and tradition, toward evolution of human knowledge. MRADI design trust on more of thirty years expertise in architectural design - structural - urban planning - plant engineering and industrial design trades. Multidisciplinary team MRADI design is the ideal partner for costumers who would like to relate in a simple and direct way with a close-knit team, which follows every design item, from concept to engineering, overlooking contracts with general contractors and suppliers, direction of construction sites and artistic supervision.   You also would like to buy any of the object from local kenyan craftsmen made under our supervision and design. Mradi Design is the right solution to get a good quality design helping to grow African Economy wherever you live.   Energy and environmental sustainability should be the focus of any MRADI design project. Doesn't matter if it will concern a small building or  a furniture or  a lamp or a landscape development. Sustainability as for communication or mobility is the main interesting factor that design should consider. Project proposals start on understanding the functionality of any object to be thought. Buildings and any designed object need to contain in itself the possibility to changes and therefore must go beyond appearance, architecture, industrial or handicraft design has  to deal with substance of shapes in order to be able to withstand fast pace of change. Simplicity is the goal that try to achieve MRADI design, overcoming the complexity of interrelationship between the various project requirements.   OUR FOCUS ON DESIGN   MRADI designS for YOU any kind of object and organize the perfect way to collect it to you. Any object will be tailored on your desire 'cause we care about your happiness and satisfaction! You will visit any of our branch activities to find your own stylish MRADI way of living. Have a nice journey on our website!   WHAT WE CAN DO FOR YOU</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/38aa4181be8b30d6e5b505654ab17e9aa1719881.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/archingstudio/mradi-designs-kenya-into-an-italianswahili-style/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78ed06b7-ec29-420a-b873-5b9835b20628</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 10:39:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[La Casa del Cardinale]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>La Casa del Cardinale</h1><p>progetto di ristrutturazione in L'Ago  La Spezia</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/554ebc5c405726f6160b2f55eda22304fd866cf4.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/archingstudio/2a199328-bc99-43f3-a31b-183351dcd3e2/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2a199328-bc99-43f3-a31b-183351dcd3e2</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 18:33:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Un mondo di professionisti e competenze per un mondo  in continuo cambiamento.   ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Un mondo di professionisti e competenze per un mondo  in continuo cambiamento.   </h1><p>Copyright © 2016 ArchingStudio. Tutti i diritti riservati. - Associazione Archingstudio - Via Cecchi 5/2 - 16129 - GENOVA - Tel. +39 0108566962 (giovedì 14.00-17.00) - Fax +39 0108561290 - segreteria@archingstudio.org Seguici su Google+</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/06ac4d91e1633b2ccea9d9cab262b7dd5d174604.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.archingstudio.org/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b284eb1a-a8e1-4897-bedb-d961c041a9bc</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 08:47:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SARUNI OCEAN RESORT]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>SARUNI OCEAN RESORT</h1><p>Luxury resort in Msambweni Kenya</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c9934e411f19d688a8702ef4f7c04c9c9bb07c46.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/archingstudio/saruni-ocean-resort/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c653a420-8ed5-4c5c-a76c-e8dcf5e8016f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 18:46:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>